<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chicago Human+AI Lab (CHAI) on Chicago Human+AI Lab</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Chicago Human+AI Lab (CHAI) on Chicago Human+AI Lab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chicagohai.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing HypoBench: Towards Systematic and Principled Benchmarking for Hypothesis Generation</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/news/250424-hypobench-website/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/news/250424-hypobench-website/</guid><description>Checkout the first principled benchmark on hypothesis generation! Paper available at: HypoBench: Towards Systematic and Principled Benchmarking for Hypothesis Generation.</description></item><item><title>Official website of: Literature Meets Data: A Synergistic Approach to Hypothesis Generation</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/news/241201-lit-plus-data-website/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/news/241201-lit-plus-data-website/</guid><description>Checkout the project website for our latest paper on hypothesis generation - Literature Meets Data: A Synergistic Approach to Hypothesis Generation!</description></item><item><title>Election NLP Project Launch</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/news/241029-election-nlp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/news/241029-election-nlp/</guid><description>We have launched our Election NLP project website! This project will showcase the possibilities of using NLP to support humans&amp;rsquo; political decision-making.</description></item><item><title>A Symposium on Communication &amp; Intelligence</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/news/240918-symposium-ci/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/news/240918-symposium-ci/</guid><description>October 18th, 2024, 9:00 AM - 5:30 PM
John Crerar Library, Room 390
Check out the Symposium Website for more information!
The Symposium on Communication &amp;amp; Intelligence is a place to discuss how to think about the intertwining of Communication and Intelligence in an age of machines that talk back. We increasingly interact with technology that attempts (simulates?) communication with humans, rather than just signaling information passively for a user to interpret.</description></item><item><title>Demo Links</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/demos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/demos/</guid><description> Election NLP Machine in the loop Retweetedmore Reddit genealogy Task delegability</description></item><item><title>People</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/people/</guid><description> Faculty Chenhao Tan Postdocs Julia Mendelsohn Cristina Garbacea PhDs Yangqiaoyu (Rosa) Zhou Karen Zhou Chacha Chen Mourad Heddaya Haokun Liu Dang Nguyen Xiaoyan (Elena) Bai Masters &amp;amp; Undergrads Yuxin (Jessica) Ji Yi Wu</description></item><item><title>Publication</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/publication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/publication/</guid><description>Preprint Emre Kıcıman, Robert Ness, Amit Sharma, and Chenhao Tan. Causal Reasoning and Large Language Models: Opening a New Frontier for Causality. Nan-Jiang Jiang, Chenhao Tan, and Marie-Catherine de Marneffe. Understanding and Predicting Human Label Variation in Natural Language Inference through Explanation. Himabindu Lakkaraju, Dylan Slack, Yuxin Chen, Chenhao Tan, and Sameer Singh. Rethinking Explainability as a Dialogue: A Practitioner&amp;rsquo;s Perspective. 2023 Karen Zhou and Chenhao Tan. Entity-Based Evaluation of Political Bias in Automatic Summarization.</description></item></channel></rss>