<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chicago Human+AI Lab (CHAI)</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Chicago Human+AI Lab (CHAI)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://chicagohai.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Demo Links</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/demos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/demos/</guid><description> Machine in the loop Retweetedmore Reddit genealogy Task delegability</description></item><item><title>News</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/news/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/news/</guid><description> Checkout this blog post for our EMNLP 2022 paper Active Example Selection for In-Context Learning! We have a postdoc opening on human-centered AI. Please email Chenhao your CV and names of references! In Fall 2022, we will also have openings for postdocs through the DSI fellowship! We gave a tutorial on human-centered evaluation of explanations at NAACL, and the recorded videos are on Youtube!</description></item><item><title>People</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/people/</guid><description> Faculty Chenhao Tan PhDs Chao-Chun (Joe) Hsu Han Liu Yangqiaoyu (Rosa) Zhou Karen Zhou Chacha Chen Mourad Heddaya Chenghao Yang Masters &amp;amp; Undergrads Grace Wang Jiamin Yang Shuyuan (Lily) Wang Dang Nguyen Yixuan (Tom) Wang Yuxin (Jessica) Ji Alumni PhDs &amp;amp; Postdocs Shi Feng (Postdoc 2023 -&amp;gt; Research Associate at NYU -&amp;gt; Assistant Professor at George Washington University) Samuel Carton (Postdoc 2022 -&amp;gt; Assistant Professor at the University of New Hampshire) Vivian Lai (PhD 2022 -&amp;gt; Research scientist at VISA research) Estelle Smith (Postdoc 2022 -&amp;gt; Assistant Professor at the Colorado School of Mines) Jason Shuo Zhang (PhD 2020 -&amp;gt; Postdoc at Max Planck Institute -&amp;gt; Machine Learning Scientist at ASOS) Master, Undergrads, and High School Students Brent DeVries (Master 2023) Zander Meitus (Master 2023) Harry Tian (Master 2023 -&amp;gt; PhD at Purdue University) Yiming Zhang (Master 2023 -&amp;gt; PhD at CMU) Kenan Tang (Undergrad 2023 -&amp;gt; PhD at UCSB) David Atkinson (Undergrad 2019, University of Colorado Boulder) Rajat Bhatnagar (Master 2021, University of Colorado Boulder) Ava Bartolome (Undergrad 2022, Clark University -&amp;gt; PhD at the University of Minnesota) Martin Chou (Undergrad 2022, Tsinghua -&amp;gt; Master at CMU) Rayan Garg (High school 2021 -&amp;gt; Undergrad at Cornell) Qitian Hu (Undergrad 2022) Zhenqi Li (Undergrad 2020, University of Colorado Boulder) Brian Lubars (Master 2019, University of Colorado Boulder) Shantanu Karnwal (Master 2019, University of Colorado Boulder) Madhusudhan Aithal Mahabhaleshwara (Master 2021, University of Colorado Boulder) Anirudh Rathore (Master 2021, University of Colorado Boulder) Kumar Bhargav Srinivasan (Master 2019, University of Colorado Boulder) Hunter Wapman (Master 2019, University of Colorado Boulder) Xiaochuang Han (Undergraduate 2019, Georgia Tech -&amp;gt; Master at CMU -&amp;gt; PhD at the University of Washington) Jie Wang (Undergrad 2020, University of Colorado Boulder)</description></item><item><title>Publication</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/publication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/publication/</guid><description>Preprint Emre Kıcıman, Robert Ness, Amit Sharma, and Chenhao Tan. Causal Reasoning and Large Language Models: Opening a New Frontier for Causality. Karen Zhou and Chenhao Tan. Characterizing Political Bias in Automatic Summaries: A Case Study of Trump and Biden. Nan-Jiang Jiang, Chenhao Tan, and Marie-Catherine de Marneffe. Understanding and Predicting Human Label Variation in Natural Language Inference through Explanation. Himabindu Lakkaraju, Dylan Slack, Yuxin Chen, Chenhao Tan, and Sameer Singh.</description></item></channel></rss>