<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chicago Human+AI Lab (CHAI)</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Chicago Human+AI Lab (CHAI)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://chicagohai.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Demo Links</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/demos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/demos/</guid><description> Machine in the loop Retweetedmore Reddit genealogy Task delegability</description></item><item><title>News</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/news/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/news/</guid><description> Checkout this blog post for our EMNLP 2022 paper Active Example Selection for In-Context Learning! We have a postdoc opening on human-centered AI. Please email Chenhao your CV and names of references! In Fall 2022, we will also have openings for postdocs through the DSI fellowship! We gave a tutorial on human-centered evaluation of explanations at NAACL, and the recorded videos are on Youtube!</description></item><item><title>People</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/people/</guid><description> Faculty Chenhao Tan PhDs Chao-Chun (Joe) Hsu Han Liu Yangqiaoyu (Rosa) Zhou Karen Zhou Chacha Chen Mourad Heddaya Chenghao Yang Masters &amp;amp; Undergrads Grace Wang Jiamin Yang Shuyuan (Lily) Wang Dang Nguyen Yixuan (Tom) Wang Yuxin (Jessica) Ji</description></item><item><title>Publication</title><link>https://chicagohai.github.io/publication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chicagohai.github.io/publication/</guid><description>Preprint Emre Kıcıman, Robert Ness, Amit Sharma, and Chenhao Tan. Causal Reasoning and Large Language Models: Opening a New Frontier for Causality. Karen Zhou and Chenhao Tan. Characterizing Political Bias in Automatic Summaries: A Case Study of Trump and Biden. Nan-Jiang Jiang, Chenhao Tan, and Marie-Catherine de Marneffe. Understanding and Predicting Human Label Variation in Natural Language Inference through Explanation. Himabindu Lakkaraju, Dylan Slack, Yuxin Chen, Chenhao Tan, and Sameer Singh.</description></item></channel></rss>